<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Niklas Arnitz</title>
    <link>//niklasarnitz.codes/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Niklas Arnitz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 15:33:22 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//niklasarnitz.codes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>//niklasarnitz.codes/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 15:33:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//niklasarnitz.codes/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I am Niklas, a software developer from Southern Germany. I love to make my daily life easier by programming and to solve daily problems with it. In my spare time I love to take pictures. Other hobbies include event technology and public relations in a Christian youth project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>//niklasarnitz.codes/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 15:33:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//niklasarnitz.codes/projects/</guid>
      <description>TODO</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legal Disclosure</title>
      <link>//niklasarnitz.codes/legal-disclosure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 15:30:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//niklasarnitz.codes/legal-disclosure/</guid>
      <description>Information in accordance with Section 5 TMG
Niklas Arnitz
Friedenstraße 30
76477 Elchesheim-Illingen
Contact Information Telephone: +49 176 41478167
E-Mail address: me@niklasarnitz.codes
Disclaimer Accountability for links
Responsibility for the content of external links (to web pages of third parties) lies solely with the operators of the linked pages. No violations were evident to us at the time of linking. Should any legal infringement become known to us, we will remove the respective link immediately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms and Conditions</title>
      <link>//niklasarnitz.codes/terms-and-conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 15:22:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//niklasarnitz.codes/terms-and-conditions/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to niklasarnitz.codes!
These terms and conditions outline the rules and regulations for the use of niklasarnitz.codes&amp;rsquo;s Website, located at niklasarnitz.codes.
By accessing this website we assume you accept these terms and conditions. Do not continue to use niklasarnitz.codes if you do not agree to take all of the terms and conditions stated on this page. Our Terms and Conditions were created with the help of the Terms And Conditions Generator and the Terms &amp;amp; Conditions Generator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Midas M32 4.0 Firmware</title>
      <link>//niklasarnitz.codes/content/posts/midas-m32-4.0-firmware/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 15:19:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//niklasarnitz.codes/content/posts/midas-m32-4.0-firmware/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Midas released Version 4.0 of its firmware for their great M32 mixer last week. Since I worked quite a bit using the new version, I would like to document some findings here.
New Features
The new 4.0 release of the M32 firmware brings many new features to the table.
The most obvious feature is the much-improved UI. The darker, more flat UI appeals to me much more than the &amp;ldquo;old&amp;rdquo; UI of the M32.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>//niklasarnitz.codes/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 15:19:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//niklasarnitz.codes/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy At niklasarnitz.codes, accessible from niklasarnitz.codes, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by niklasarnitz.codes and how we use it.
If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) We are a Data Controller of your information.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>